var questions = [
    {
        question:"The function and var are known as:",
        answer: ["Keywords","Data types","Declaration statements"],
        correct: "Declaration statements"
    },
    {
        question: "Which type of JavaScript language is ___",
        answer: ["Object-Oriented","Object-Based","Assembly-language"],
        correct: "Object-Based"
    },
    {
        question:"Which of the following variables takes precedence over the others if the names are the same?",
        answer: ["Global variable","The local element","The two of the above","None of the above"],
        correct: "The local element"  
    },
    {
        question: "Which one of the following is the correct way for calling the JavaScript code?",
        answer: ["Preprocessor","Triggering Event","RMI","Function/Method"],
        correct: "Function/Method"
    },
    {
        
        question: "Which of the following number object function returns the value of the number?",
        answer: ["toString()","valueOf()","toLocaleString()"],
        correct: "valueOf()"
    },
    {
        question: "In JavaScript the x===y statement implies that:",
        answer: ["Both x and y are equal in value, type and reference address as well","Both are x and y are equal in value only","Both are equal in the value and data type","Both are not same at all."],
        correct: "Both are equal in the value and data type."
    },
    {
        question: "Which one of the following is an ternary operator?",
        answer: ["?",":","-","+"],
        correct: "?"
    },
    {
        
        question: "Which one of the following is known as the Equality operator, which is used to check whether the two values are equal or not:",
        answer: ["=","===","==","&&"],
        correct: "=="
    },
    {
        
        question: "Which one of the following operator returns false if both values are equal?",
        answer: ["!","!==","!="],
        correct: "!="
    },
    {
        
        question: "In a case, where the value of the operator is NULL , the typeof returned by the unary operator is___.",
        answer:["undefined","string","boolean","object"],
        correct: "object"
    },
]
